keepkidshealthy.com 2005-12-13

# Privacy Policy at Keep Kids Healthy

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. keepkidshealthy.com shall collect no personal information about you except when specifically and knowingly provide by you. 

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**  
We do not currently collect any personal information from the visitors to our web site.

When you place an order through one of our affiliates, all information is sent to amazon.com, drugstore.com, or whatever dealer you are ordering from. No information is collected by this web site. Please see our sponsors respective privacy statements for more information. While they do report to us which items have been ordered, they do not include any personal information that would identify who the buyer is. And no credit card information is sent back to this web site!

 **What about the mailing list and newsletters?**  
The Keep Kids Healthy mailing list is for updating subscribers to new and updated information and available on Keep Kids Healthy. The addresses of subscribers will not be sold, traded or rented to others.  

**What about our advertisers?**  
Keep Kids Healthy makes use of third party companies to serve banner ads on our site. These companies, including Double Click, often use cookies and gather information to track the effectiveness of these banners. This information shared with DoubleClick (or “third party” advertiser) is non-personally-identifiable. This information collected from customer’s visit to this site and other sites is used to serve ads on this site and other sites. Visitors can choose not to have their information shared with 3rd party advertiser(s), i.e., “opt out”; and may view the [DoubleClick Privacy Policy](http://www.sonar.com/naiprivacy).  

**How do we protect customer information?**  
The only way that we can see your e-mail address is if you e-mail us a question or comment. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

**What about "cookies"?**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. This web site does use cookies in the Baby Name Finder and the voting and survey programs to help keep track of the names that you vote for and whether or not you have voted. Cookies can also be set by the Parent's Forum bulletin board.

**Will we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.  

**In summary**  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, on our home page, and in our newsletters, so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Tell us what you think**  
We welcome your questions and comments about privacy. Please [contact us](http://www.keepkidshealthy.com/welcome/contactus.html) if you have any questions or concerns about your privacy.
